

José Raimundo del Rio

Software Full Stack Developer

- irdelriodom@gmail.com
- Barcelona, España
- Medium
- **GitHub**

- +34683340572
- 🚗 Licencia Clase B
- in LinkedIn
- **★** Web Profile

EDUCATION

Full Stack Software Developer

4Geeks Academy

2022 - 2023

Full Stack Certificate. Six months long course with weekly personal projects. Learned tools: **ReactJS**, **Bootstrap** y **responsive websites**. Backend con **Python**, **Flask**, **MySQL** and **nodeJs**.

Civil Engineer in Construction

Pontificia Universidad Católica

2011 - 2020 | Santiago, Chile

Bachelor of Construction Engineering with a distinction vote.

Certificaciones

Oficial online courses

- Full Stack Software Developer 4Geeks Academy
- IT Automation with Python Google Academy
- Python Programming Wesleyan University
- Python Coding Mastermind Academy
- Basic HTML y and CSS3 Mastermind Academy

LANGUAGES

- Inglés
- Portugués
- Español

PROFILE

I have more than 2 years studying programming on my own, and now I am already formally graduated from the 4Geeks academy. My hobbies are music, movies, cycling and studying new things.

I live in Europe 1 year ago. I seek to expand my cultural horizons.

SKILLS

Technology

Python - javaScript - Web Scrapping - Regular Expressions - Microsoft Excel - OOP - Git - API - SQL -Flask - ReactJS - REVIT

Soft Skills

I'm excelent at working in teamwork, I have a good relationship with people, closeness, nice, very friendly. Good experience with conflict resolution.

Music

Folk singer. I play the guitar, the piano and sing at parties, birthdays and events.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

4Geeks Academy

Teacher Assistant

05/2023 - present | Barcelona, Spain

Keeping all the classes uploaded in the channel, review the projects by students and be available to solve doubts and schedule mentories to help the students.

4Geeks Academy

4Geeks blog Copywriter

2022 - 2023

Writing articles for the official blog of the 4Geeks Academy website.

PROJECTS

Alien Invasion

Videogame. Created with PyGame.

Bingo Card Generator 🛮

Bingo cardboard generator app. Python.

Photosize 2

App to calculate sizes, pixels and resolutions of photos and digital drawings.